        // Here is an array of questions, we can add or subtract questions as we see fit

        var quizQuestions = [
            {
                question: "What was the first location selected for a Real Housewives franchise?",
                choices: ["New York", "Orange County", "Atlanta", "Miami"],
                correctAnswer: "Orange County"
            },
            {
                question: "Who was NOT an original member of the O.C. cast?",
                choices: ["Jo De La Rosa", "Brandi Glanville", "Vicki Gunvalson", "Jeana Keough"],
                correctAnswer: "Brandi Glanville"
            },
            {
                question: "What community did the original O.C. housewives live in?",
                choices: ["Casa Mia", "Calabasas", "Casa del Sol", "Coto De Caza"],
                correctAnswer: "Coto De Caza"
            },
            {
                question: "What sport was Jeana Keough's husband involved in?",
                choices: ["Basketball", "Baseball", "Football", "Hockey"],
                correctAnswer: "Baseball"
            },
            {
                question: "What location of the series introduced the world to Bethenny Frankel?",
                choices: ["Atlanta", "New York", "Miami", "D.C."],
                correctAnswer: "New York"
            },
            {
                question: "What housewife is frequently referred to as 'the Countess'?",
                choices: ["Kim Zolciak", "Joanna Krupa", "LuAnn DeLesseps", "Nene Leakes"],
                correctAnswer: "LuAnn DeLesseps"
            },
            {
                question: "Who is the FIRST person Bethenny orders to 'go to sleep' in one famous on-screen argument?",
                choices: ["Jill Zarin", "Sonja Morgan", "Kelly Bensimon", "Alex McCord"],
                correctAnswer: "Kelly Bensimon"
            },
            {
                question: "What did Aviva Drescher throw across the table during a famous fight scene on the show?",
                choices: ["a glass", "a table", "money", "her leg"],
                correctAnswer: "her leg"
            },
            {
                question: "What franchise of the show introduced NeNe Leakes to the world?",
                choices: ["Miami", "Atlanta", "D.C.", "Potomac"],
                correctAnswer: "Atlanta"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the name of Dina Manzo's hairless cat?",
                choices: ["Aunt Jemima", "Mr. Buttons", "Grandma Wrinkles", "Kitty Cat"],
                correctAnswer: "Grandma Wrinkles"
            },
            {
                question: "Which Atlanta housewife was confused about the operation of the Underground Railroad?",
                choices: ["Porsha Williams", "Shere√© Whitfield", "NeNe Leakes", "Kenya Moore"],
                correctAnswer: "Porsha Williams"
            },
            {
                question: "Who was NOT an original member of the New Jersey cast?",
                choices: ["Melissa Gorga", "Danielle Staub", "Teresa Giudice", "Jacqueline Laurita"],
                correctAnswer: "Melissa Gorga"
            },
            {
                question: "What New Jersey housewife spent a year in jail in 2015?",
                choices: ["Caroline Manzo", "Teresa Giudice", "Kathy Wakile", "Danielle Staub"],
                correctAnswer: "Teresa Giudice"
            },
            {
                question: "What is Ashley Darby's drink of choice?",
                choices: ["Martini", "Corona", "Pinot Grigio", "Cosmo"],
                correctAnswer: "Corona"
            },
            {
                question: "Which member of the New Jersey cast got a spinoff show in 2014?",
                choices: ["Teresa Giudice", "Melissa Gorga", "Caroline Manzo", "Dina Manzo"],
                correctAnswer: "Caroline Manzo"
            },
            {
                question: "What year did 'The Real Housewives of D.C.' premiere?",
                choices: ["2006", "2008", "2010", "2012"],
                correctAnswer: "2010"
            },
            {
                question: "What season did Lisa Vanderpump appear on?",
                choices: ["Orange County", "Beverly Hills", "Hollywood", "Miami"],
                correctAnswer: "Beverly Hills"
            },
            {
                question: "What country is New York City's Alex McCord's husband from?",
                choices: ["England", "New Zealand", "Australia", "Denmark"],
                correctAnswer: "Australia"
            },
            {
                question: "Which location has NOT been a 'RH-vacay spot on 'RHONJ'?",
                choices: ["Florida", "Paris", "Italy", "Napa"],
                correctAnswer: "Paris"
            },
            {
                question: "Which hit single did Kandi NOT help write?",
                choices: ["Waterfalls", "Bills, Bills, Bills", "No Scrubs", "There You Go"],
                correctAnswer: "Waterfalls"
            },
            {
                question: "Which housewife has NOT released a song since her time on air?",
                choices: ["Kim Z", "LuAnn", "Melissa", "Brandi"],
                correctAnswer: "Brandi"
            },
            {
                question: "Finish this sentence: 'Prostitution whore. You were fucking engaged ____.'",
                choices: ["12 times", "17 times", "19 times", "21 times"],
                correctAnswer: "19 times"
            },
            {
                question: "How many brunette Housewives have been on 'RHOC'?",
                choices: ["five", "six", "seven", "eight"],
                correctAnswer: "eight"
            },
            {
                question: "What did Teresa G. accuse her sister-in-law Melissa of?",
                choices: ["being a stripper", "being a gold digger", "copying everything she does", "all of the above"],
                correctAnswer: "all of the above"
            },
            {
                question: "What color dress was Kelly wearing during her 'breakthrough' on Scary Island?",
                choices: ["red", "orange", "purple", "green"],
                correctAnswer: "purple"
            },
            {
                question: "Many Housewives got their start modeling. Who didn't?",
                choices: ["Vicki", "Cynthia", "Brandi", "Joanna"],
                correctAnswer: "Vicki"
            },
            {
                question: "Who was NOT an original member of the Miami cast?",
                choices: ["Lisa Hochstein", "Adriana de Moura", "Alexia Echevarria", "Marysol Patton"],
                correctAnswer: "Lisa Hochstein"
            },
            {
                question: "What location was chosen for the eighth incarnation of the series?",
                choices: ["Potomac", "Seattle", "Miami", "Dallas"],
                correctAnswer: "Potomac"
            },
            {
                question: "What location featured housewife Gretchen Rossi?",
                choices: ["Dallas", "Beverly Hills", "Potomac", "Orange County"],
                correctAnswer: "Orange County"
            },
            {
                question: "How many Real Housewives cities are there currently?",
                choices: ["four", "six", "seven", "ten"],
                correctAnswer: "seven"
            }
        ];